English

My account

* Why itsme®
    
* Get started

Privacy Policy
==============

#### of the itsme® app

Just to be very clear: itsme® takes your trust and privacy very seriously and processes your personal data only as necessary for our itsme® App.If you use itsme®’s services through our App, you agree to this Privacy policy.

itsme® changes its Privacy policy every so often. We will inform you through the app for any significant change, and you can always consult our website to get he most recent version. This document is the legal text. To make it easy and more understandably for you, we summarized above Privacy policy into simple speak below.

**What kind of Personal Data itsme****®** **deals with?**

itsme® is all about identity, security and privacy. We need at a minimum the following data to offer you the itsme®service(s):

* Identification data: Basically the information as on your eID card
    
* Security data: to protect you and the online services you use through itsme®, we use information from your smartphone. This includes your location, as in: country indication only
    
* Transactions: you will be able to proof what you did, or did not, confirm to with itsme®, up to 10 years after your last use of our service
    
* Enrolment data: information on your initial enrolment to itsme®.

**Why and how itsme****®** **uses your data?**

In the first place, we use your data to perform the itsme® services you want: share data (only if you agree), login, confirm transactions  
This includes archiving for evidentiary purposes  
Also:

* To keep you informed of changes to the itsme® services
    
* To respond to questions you may have
    
* To check the use of the itsme® services, also after marketing campaigns
    
* To analyse, evaluate and improve our itsme® services

Note that the data that we collected for the use of the App will not be used by us for direct marketing

**You are in control of your data, anytime, anywhere**

* You can access your data via the App and update it
    
* You can block your itsme® services at any time
    
* You can have your data removed from our operational systems

**How itsme****®** **protects your data**

* We at Belgian Mobile ID always encrypt your data, when stored or when communicated to a service provider (if - and only if - you agreed to it, offcourse)
    
* Your data is, very, securely stored in the safest Data Center in Europe we could find.
    
* We went so far as to have external auditors validate our security: check our [ISO 27001 certification](https://www.itsme.be/en/blog/iso27001)

### Legal information

About itsme®
------------

#### My itsme® account

More info
---------

Legal info
----------

* Manage privacy preferences

#### Follow itsme® on

© 2024 Belgian Mobile ID SA/NV - Rue du Marquis 1, 1000 Brussels - VAT BE0541.659.084

* 

### Choose your region
